http://www.nasmhpd.org/content/nasmhpd-online-privacy-policy

National Association of State Mental Health Program Directors
Division of Recovery Support Services
Affiliate OrganizationsCultural and Linguistic Competence Coordinators' Network
Multi-State Disaster Behavioral Health Consortium
The National Coalition on Mental Health and Deaf Individuals
State Hospital Organizations
NASMHPD Task ForcesHousing Task Force
NASMHPD President's Task Force on Returning Veterans
Rosters
Technical AssistanceEmployment Development Initiative (EDI)
Technical Assistance for State Mental Health Agencies
NASMHPD’s Center for Innovation in Behavioral Health Policy and PracticeTIC Videos and Webinars
Transformation Transfer Initiative
Early Intervention in PsychosisWhat is Psychosis?
MISSION
NASMHPD will work with states, federal partners, and stakeholders to promote wellness, recovery, and resiliency for individuals with mental health conditions or co-occurring mental health and substance related disorders across all ages and cultural groups, including: youth, older persons, veterans and their families, and people under the jurisdiction of the court.
DETAILS
Commissioners
Boards of Directors
NASMHPD Commissioners
Divisions and Councils
Children, Youth and Families Division
Forensic Division
Older Persons Division
Multi-State Disaster Behavioral Health Consortium
The National Coalition on Mental Health and Deaf Individuals
State Hospital Organizations
NASMHPD Task Forces
Housing Task Force
NASMHPD President's Task Force on Returning Veterans
Rosters
Technical Assistance
Employment Development Initiative (EDI)
Technical Assistance for State Mental Health Agencies
NASMHPD’s Center for Innovation in Behavioral Health Policy and Practice
TIC Videos and Webinars
Transformation Transfer Initiative
TTI 2019 Bed Registry Project Report
TTI Social Marketing Materials
TTI Information Exchanges
TTI Virtual Technical Assistance Sessions
Early Intervention in Psychosis
What is Psychosis?
About EDIPPP
Information for Providers
Information for Individuals and Families
Research
Information for Policymakers
Treatment Programs
Outreach & Awareness
Crisis Now: Dedicated to Transforming Mental Health Systems
NASMHPD Online Privacy Policy
The National Association of State Mental Health Program Directors (NASMHPD) thanks you for visiting our Web site. At NASMHPD we respect your privacy, and so we want you to know that during your visit to our site, you may be providing information to NASMHPD in two ways: 1) Anonymous statistics collected as you browse the site, and 2) Personal information you knowingly give us. We want you to be aware of how we handle this information.
Anonymous Statistics
As you browse the site, NASMHPD's computers collect information about your visit, not about you personally. Using Web server logs, we monitor anonymous statistics such as:
How many people visit our site
Which pages people visit on our site
Which browsers people use to visit our site
We use these statistics to improve our Web site, monitor its performance, and to make it easier for you and other visitors to use. None of this information is associated with you personally. Please note that you do not give us your identity by visiting our Web site, however, you do identify yourself by sending us e-mail (see Personal Information, below, for more information).
Personal Information
Within this Web site, you may be asked to give us personal information, such as when you ask a question via e-mail that requires a response or when you login to our member section to adjust your contact information. This information may include your ZIP code or e-mail address, for instance.
We want to be very clear: NASMHPD will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. We will not sell or give away names, addresses or any information about our site users to any third parties.
Content Disclaimer
This Web site is produced and maintained by NASMHPD and its subcontractors. The site's content is solely the responsibility of NASMHPD and does not necessarily represent the position of the United States federal government, including the Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration (SAMHSA) or its centers.
Internet Disclaimer
NASMHPD assumes responsibility only for the information it provides on its home pages. As a convenience to you, there are links throughout this site that will allow you to leave NASMHPD's site. You should be aware that any sites linked here are not under the control of NASMHPD. As such, we can make no representation to you concerning the content of these sites, nor does the fact that NASMHPD has provided a link to a site serve as an endorsement by NASMHPD of any of these sites. You should also be aware that the privacy protections afforded by the NASMHPD site may not be afforded by sites linked to NASMHPD.
Your Privacy is Important to Us
NASMHPD values your privacy, and one of our most important goals is to protect your privacy while you enjoy our Web site. Your information will be protected as described unless the specific Web page says otherwise. Should this privacy policy be modified in the future, this Web page will reflect the revised policy.
If you have any further questions about your privacy and the National Association of State Mental Health Program Directors, please e-mail us atwebmaster@nasmhpd.org, or call us at 703-739-9333. For more information on privacy issues in general, visit the Federal Trade Commission Web site at http://www.ftc.gov.
